(Watch on KonFlix.vip)
Guys, I think we’re almost there.
Guys, wait!
Are you sure this is the right way?
Hell University.
You all need to register.
Remember...
This university changes at 7:00 p.m..
Be careful.
Hello, newbies.
I am Madam Violet.
Headmistress of Hell University.
7 pm to 5 am is what we call Freedom Night
Also known as Bloody Night
Everything is free.
You are free to do whatever you want.
Killing is allowed.
So I suggest that you stay in your rooms...
Lock up your doors,
and don't go out.
What did we get ourselves into?
What if something bad happens to us?
Jerome, it’s Mia!
Why aren't they fazed by death?
What the hell is wrong
with this university?!
They did it again.
Who did this?
Black Blood Gang.
That nail in his tongue is their symbol.
Another war will happen soon...
And I know this war will be bloodier
now that they've killed Raze
Silvenia's one and only brother.
Raze Silvenia?
The leader of the Devil God Warrior.
Good morning, class. I hope I'm not late.
Yes, you are, Mr. Dimatalo.
You know Supremo hates people who are late.
Who’s this girl?
And what’s with her attitude?
And who is this “Supremo”
she’s talking about?
You're right, Ms. Nicky. So-sorry...
Ahh class...
We'll begin our lecture in a while.
Ahh... please bring out your algebra books.
Algrebra is about finding the unknown.
In this class...
I will teach you how to find X...
and Y.
Do you know everything?
What is this girl taking about?
Why won’t she leave me alone?
If m equals three and x is equals five
and b is equals six. We will find the y...
I said... do you know everything?
No, I don't.
But I'll figure it out on my own.
I don't need anything from you.
Your curiousity will kill you, Zein.
Suit yourself...
If you really want to know the
truth, you must find it yourself.
Or you can have it the easy way...
break the only rule.
Can you just leave me alone?
If I'm curious about something...
I'll figure it out on my own.
Do you hear how pathetic you sound?
Well anyway...
If you don't want to die early...
I would just obey the
rules and shut my mouth.
Who are you?
Let's just say...
I'm one of the big dogs here.
And no one...
talks back to me
like what you’ve been doing.
But I got to say...
I kind of admire your...
tenacity, Ms. Zein Shion.
You have my attention.
I wonder...
what reckless thing you'll do next.
This girl is really testing me.
But there’s things I want to
find out about this university too.
Fine.
Just do it, Zein.
I want to know what the
deal is with this university?
Miss Shion!
Are you ready to listen
and be part of this class!?
Yes, Sir. Sorry.
Shit! Did you see that?
There's so much blood!
Jerome, please!
Shut up! You're making it worse!
So annoying!
I'm sorry!
How about the guy with red hair?
Did you see him too?
Are you sure about what you saw, Mia?
Cause we really didn't notice anyone.
Isn't it because of the dead body we saw?
That's why you keep seeing
things that aren't there?
No!
I'm sure. I saw him.
Then he just disappeared.
Huh?
Don't worry about it, Mia!
If his hair is red...
we can easily spot him.
Because...
his hair is red!
Huh?
You're saying stupid shit again!
Guys!
Zein's not here!
What!?
What do you mean Zein's not here?
Where could she be?
She told us we would meet here!
[beeping]
Are you ready to die?
You've got some nerve, huh?
You think you can outdo me?
I've killed many people.
Do you want to be added in the list?
Am I right?
Who are you?
You want to know my name?
I'm Nicky Colt.
Listen well next time, bitch!
Where could Zein be?
She should be here by now.
Hey!
Worried much?
You know how Matt gets if it's about Zein.
He likes her?
Matt, you're overexaggerating! Calm down.
Chill! Don't overthink it.
I'm not overthinking!
I'm worried about her! I don't want
anything bad happening to her...
I need to find her!
You can't skip class, Matt!
You know it's against the rules!
And everyone's eyes are on us.
You might get hurt.
You're being too much!
You're so overprotective!
This lover boy can't help it.
He’ll go against all odds for Zein!
What if you had to go
through Bloody Night for her?
Will you still save her?
Of course!
But not just for her...
I'll do it for all of us.
We're all in this together, right?
Chill.
I'm just making you laugh.
She'll be here.
Don't worry too much.
Speaking of Bloody Night...
So, what's the plan?
Are we going to coop up in the dorms again?
Of course! Isn't that obvious?
We’re safer there.
But...
But aren’t you curious what it's like to
be on the ground during Bloody Night?
What if...
Let's go out for a bit tonight?
I want to see everything up close.
Are you serious, Dave?
Do you have a death wish?
Of course not!
Maybe the red-haired guy
you're so curious about is there!
The one you keep looking for?
Oh no!
Someone's being jealous!
Really?
But you know guys?
Dave has a point.
Until when are we hiding every 7:00 p.m.?
I admit... I'm curious too!
But our safety is our priority!
Right!
And we're newbies here.
Their eyes are set on us.
We can't trust anybody here, remember?
So that's it?
We'll always hide?
Exactly, it's better!
Unless you want to face
those killers head on?
We need to stay together, okay?
We can't leave without
Zein on Bloody Night.
It's too dangerous!
Don't you have class?
Full name, please.
Zein.
Zein Shion.
Boo!
Nice.
What's your problem?
Don't you still have class to attend to?
Why are you here?
Why do you care?
This is your first warning, Ms. Shion.
Once, I see you out here
again during class hours...
I'll make sure to break your arm off.
Who are you!?
Ace Craige.
The Supreme Student Government
President of Hell University.
Supreme Student Government President?
Nice meeting you, Ms. Shion.
Who is he?
Is he the one they're afraid of?
Supremo?
Physics helps us understand
how the body responds to external forces.
Like for example,
when someone gets
bruises from a tight grip...
that's force and pressure in action.
Concentrated force
damages tiny blood vessels
and the longer it is applied
the more severe the injury.
- Ms. Kath?
- Yes?
So the stronger the punch?
The harder the fall?
Jerome!
If that's what you understood
from my discussion, Jerome
I won't correct you.
But don't come crying to
me when you fail my subject.
Nice of you to join us, Ms. Shion.
Sorry.
Zein!
What's this?
What happened to you?
Why is your arm bruised?
What happened?
That looks different...
Zein, who did this?
Tell me.
May I see that, Ms. Shion?
That's the first warning.
Use this.
But remember this,
warning number two means
a more severe punishment.
What are you talking about, Ms. Kath?
Who did that to you?
Supremo.
Don't make any more offenses.
Next time, you won't be as lucky.
Supremo?
Who's that?
Ace Craige.
Okay, back to our lesson!
Where have you been?
I was worried sick.
Don't worry...
this is nothing.
You know how this place
is filled with bastards.
But I'm okay.
Don't worry.
You're sure?
Next time, don't go anywhere without me.
Okay?
Your curiousity will kill you, Zein.
Suit yourself...
If you really want to know the
truth, you must find it yourself.
Or you can have it the easy way...
break the only rule.
This school has too many secrets.
One wrong move
could put us in danger.
But if I don't do anything,
how will we ever get out?
Matt?
Zein.
See you later.
Who are they?
What do they need from you?
They're just looking for trouble.
Don't mind them.
Are they bothering you?
No, they're not.
Don't worry about me.
Don't stray away from the group.
Are you serious, Zein?
Shouldn't I be the one telling you that?
Let's go.
Last night, we confirmed ten deaths.
There were a few minor casualties.
All were contained,
except for the public display
orchestrated by the Black Blood Gang.
It's actually fifteen deaths.
The worst one was Rouge Silvenia.
Fifteen?
That's wasn't in my report!
You should double
check your report, Fritzy.
Anyways, continue.
They’re growing more rebellious, Supremo.
If this continues,
given the Bloody Night's history...
it's only a matter of time before
Devil God Warrior decides to retaliate.
We can't afford a war
between the two gangs.
Especially now.
I agree, Supremo.
These newbies can be a nuisance.
You all remember what happened
the last time a newbie
entered Hell University, right?
Wait!
The newbies aren't in my report either.
How are you aware of them?
As the Vice President of the
Supreme Student Government,
second-in-command to Supremo,
it's natural that I know all the
newbies entering Hell University.
You should've been
aware of the newbies too...
Fritzy.
Why weren't you informed?
You know...
there seems to be a lot of...
inconsistencies with your reports lately.
Don't make me regret
appointing you as my secretary.
So...
how are the newbies adjusting?
So far, they're okay.
They're quiet.
They keep to themselves.
And they're not actively
participating during the Bloody Night.
Quiet?
Keep to themselves?
Nothing?
Actually...
there's one.
There’s this girl…
I heard from some students
that she's stubborn and rebellious.
Rebellious?
How exactly?
According to the report...
she wandered off during
her first night in the campus.
She and her friend almost got injured.
Some students even witnessed that
Zein talks and fights back
to anyone who tries her.
At least, that's their initial vibe.
She was even late for one of her classes.
She seems to not care about the rules.
Even the looming danger
of the Bloody Night...
she seems not to care.
I'm sure you'll easily spot her.
Interesting.
Supremo... maybe she just wants attention?
There's always someone
like that every year.
Maybe...
Maybe not.
Keep an eye on her.
I want to know everything.
Why?
Just do it!
Copy, Supremo!
Let's see
how long until she breaks.
6:20 pm
There's still enough time to go
back to the dorm before Bloody Night.
I'm going to the bathroom.
Where do you think you're going?
Hey! Are you stupid?
You know how dangerous it is in a few
minutes and you're prioritizing peeing?
Zein, be for real!
Do you have a death wish, Zein?
I can just kill you right now!
Do you really want to die?
You're all exaggerating!
I just need to go to the bathroom!
I really need to pee!
I'll be fast!
Please!
Zein, I'll go with you.
Are you serious?
You two are being stupid! Suit yourselves!
Let them be, Van.
They can take care of themselves.
And they still have time before 7:00 p.m..
Ugh!
Right?
Right.
Just be aware of the
time and be careful, okay?
Ms. Shion?
I see one warning isn't enough for you?
I just need to go to
the bathroom, Ms. Kath.
Is that against the rules?
Of course not.
Go ahead.
Just do it fast and keep
your curiosity to yourselves.
It’s starting to get dangerous out
there, and I’m sure you’re aware of that.
Come on.
We'll go ahead.
Stop worrying, Van.
I'm so annoyed.
You’re so stubborn.
I can go to the bathroom on my own.
Look around...
there's no one here.
Safe.
You know there's no
area here that's safe, right?
It's better that the
two of us stay together.
I always want to be sure
that I can protect you.
Just wait for me here, okay?
Be careful, okay? Hurry up!
I'm serious, be careful.
I will.
What's the deal with this
school? And with Ace?
What has he done to make
everyone so afraid of him?
Who are the people that built this school?
Who are the members of the Black Blood Gang
and Devil God Warrior?
Your curiousity will kill you, Zein.
If you really want to know the truth...
you must find it yourself.
Or you can have it the easy way...
break the only rule.
What's the rule Nicky keeps talking about?
I'm only aware of Hell
University's one and only rule.
I need to know.
But how?
Do I have to go out during
Bloody Night to find out?
But we’re surrounded by demons.
What will happen to me if I do that?
Shit!
Matt?
Zein, it's 7:00 p.m..
They're out here for blood.
We need to leave before they surround us.
Matt-
We need to escape.
We need to find Mia and the others.
We need to hide if we
still want to live, Zein!
Let's go?
Be careful.
Be quiet.
Hey!
Shit!
Go after them!
Move faster! They're coming, Matt!
Matt! They're coming!
Please!
Matt, faster!
Faster, hurry up!
They're coming, Matt!
Are you done?
Please!
Zein, whatever happens
don't let go of my hand, okay?
Are we going to survive this, Matt?
Just trust me!
Let's go!
Come, let's go!
Faster!
Where are they?
They're not here!
Come on!
Aren't we going to look for Matt and Zein?
Van, we don't have time!
We need to hurry!
What if they need our help?
We can't stay here!
It's too dangerous!
Black Blood Gang.
One of the two most feared
gangs here in Hell University.
There's more I want to know about them,
And their rival gang Devil God Warrior.
But it's hard to ask
around in this university.
You cannot trust anybody.
I can only trust Matt and the others.
Matt,
this is our chance to search for answers.
Are you being serious right now?
We almost died.
We'll die eventually
if we continue being blinded by the truth.
We need to find the truth about this place
to find a way out.
Zein...
You'll get hurt if you do that.
Do you want to end up like
Rouge Silvenia? Or worse?
Huh?
Please, Zein.
Le'ts go back to the dorm, please!
Please listen to me.
Matt, please.
Please, listen
I can’t do it
This is our chance
to find out the truth!
Please, Matt.
Zein, we need to go back to the dorm!
It'll be more dangerous
as the night falls.
Please!
No, Matt.
We need to know the truth.
You know, Zein.
I'm ready to tell you all that I know...
but please don't do this,
I'm begging you.
Please, Zein.
What you did earlier,
don’t do it again,
Please.
Wait...
Does Matt know something
about this university?
How?
Zein...
Zein, I think they're gone.
Let's go?
Okay.
Matt...
Be careful.
Zein, it hurts!
What happened?
Matt?
What happened to you?
- Zein, my leg hurts!
- Can you still walk?
Zein, I can't walk.
My foot is getting numb.
No...
Zein, save yourself.
What?
Just leave me here.
No, Matt. I won't do that.
I'm not leaving you.
This is my fault.
Zein, please.
What happened, Matt?
It hurts...
Matt, please.
Be okay, please.
Please be okay.
I'm so cold...
What are you doing here?
Leave us alone!
We didn't do anything wrong to you.
Zein...
What are you doing here?!
Leave us alone!
We didn't do anything wrong!
One...
( Watch on www.kissasia.co, .club, .be, .org, .net, .id, .xyz )
Two...
Three!
One!
Two!
Three!
- Where have you been?
- Hurry!
Hurry!
Didn't you check the time!?
Come on!
Wait!
Close it!
Hurry up!
Lift the table! Help me!
Guys, come on!
One, two, three!
Lift it!
What are you doing?
Okay!
Hurry!
Get the tables!
Get out of the way!
Hurry!
Hurry, come on!
Hurry
Let's get the sofa!
Hurry!
Hurry up, Dave!
What's happening?
Dave... Hurry!
Hurry, Dave!
Get that too!
Faster! We can use that too!
- Wait!
- Get that one, hurry!
Jerome!
- Jerome!
- Hurry!
You're too loud!
Can't you calm down a bit?
If we fully cover this,
we can't see what's going on out there!
Matt and Zein are still out there!
Do you want them to die?
You’re right,
I forgot about them.
You're so smart, Dave.
But where the hell are they?
They should be here by now!
- What if they came across
- Where is Zein and Matt?
The Black Blood Gang?
Mia!
Don't say such things!
What if they're dead!?
That's not going to happen!
Mia!
How do you really feel?
Huh?
Earlier, you were worried about them.
And now you're saying they could be dead?
I don't know, okay?
I don't know!
My head is spiraling, Jerome!
I'm so scared!
I don't know if you've noticed but,
people are killing each other outside!
So sorry...
I just want all
of us to survive this night!
All of us!
- Jerome!
- Is that bad?
We're all scared right now, okay?
All of us are worried!
But please...
Show some empathy.
Can you do that?
Sorry...
I just want us to survive.
That's all I want.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Mia.
Okay.
You're both right!
We just all want to survive...
panicking won’t help any of us.
Let's just trust that they'll come back.
Everything will be okay.
Zein and Matt are strong.
The two of them can survive this.
I believe in them.
They'll return.
They will return.
Okay? They'll return.
They're here!
Wait...
Who's the red masked guy?
Matt's unconscious.
What happened to Matt?
Matt!
Wake him up!
- Matt...
- Please...
What happened to the two you?
The Black Blood Gang saw us.
They stabbed Matt with a nail.
A nail?
But his wound is just small...
Why does he look like
he’s already dying?
Matt...
Matt!
I thought so too...
- The wound is so small.
- I don't understand.
But he couldn't walk and fainted.
Then he saved us...
Let the wound bleed.
Clean it with warm water until
the poison is removed.
That's all?
No medicine?
Mia...
Put the ointment on his wound.
When it's clean... bandage it.
If your friend is strong...
he will survive.
Matt...
You can survive this!
Matt is strong!
Matt, we're here.
We're safe.
Don't give up.
Don't worry.
Where did he go?
Where is he?
What is he? A ninja?
It might be Raze Silvenia.
The leader...
of Devil God Warrior.
But why did he save us?
We entered this place
without knowing anything...
we don't know their history,
who runs the school...
We need information.
I'll ask you, Zein...
Are you ready to trade your life
with the information I'm about to give you?
I am so happy to announce,
on behalf of the Hell U administration,
that we will be having another...
Acquaintance Party!
This is the right time to celebrate
Especially now,
after all the deaths these past few weeks.
Besides,
the late headmaster...
recently died.